{
    "id": "14a1941887d94b4eba361436077890cc",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ..................... . up several times in the night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "woke",
                "have waken",
                "had woken"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "935054a31bf041ab8f465ba5cfe96b0f"
        },
        {
            "question": "My mother ....................... delicious meals.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cook",
                "cooks",
                "have cooked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "874bdd9b018f444e82494d3619e8aa44"
        },
        {
            "question": "She .....................… the answer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not knows",
                "do not know",
                "does not know"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fa554963dfb347ef9dd816d9de911a86"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys ....................... in the garden when it started raining.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are playing",
                "were playing",
                "played"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b9be0a26be744d8ab720898473001e38"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................... .. for him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wait",
                "am waiting",
                "have waited"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cdecdbf5d29a4262826a1018931796f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …..................... . the parcel yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "receive",
                "had received",
                "received"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "de66616a378a4a09a1e5f907c41e7f7a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .....................…… that movie three times.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "watched",
                "have watched",
                "had watched"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0a3c69064bc8410691ed33c684cd27dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Goats and cows .....................… us milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gives",
                "give",
                "gave"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c1d63411796143d2b6297f5d987b7dd0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Cows ..................... .. on grass.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "feeds",
                "feed",
                "fed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6b0304edffa0427487142bb9f0757092"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …..................... . for his call since yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "waited",
                "am waiting",
                "have been waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "34d4b8329f6d409a8bdf3455b39e5764"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .....................…… all the books written by Dickens.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "read",
                "am reading",
                "have read"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "54096259b71249e09b28370ade6218fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ...................... in two films.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "acted",
                "has acted",
                "acts"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "18c99e1432be442984cba27c23278cf8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ....................... nice portraits.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "draw",
                "draws",
                "has drawn"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e46ecea92ddc4d27a2f19d88e2deb6bb"
        }
    ]
}